https://lyrictheatre.co.uk/privacy-policy/

SIGN UP
https://lyrictheatre.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Privacy-Policy-TinyJPG.jpg
Privacy & Cookies Policy
Privacy and Cookies Policy
At the Lyric Theatre, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our visitors to the theatre, our website, and our email subscribers. Here you’ll find information on how we collect, store and treat personal information and data, including when we’ll contact you and website cookies.
Purchasing Tickets
When purchasing tickets at Box Office, you have the option to give us your personal information. When purchasing tickets online you must create an account, providing us with your personal information, in order for us to process the ticket order. This personal information will be stored on the Spektrix Ticketing System and not shared with any third party organisation. You have the opportunity to review your personal information through your account and make necessary amendments at any time. You also have the opportunity to delete your account at any time. When creating your account, you will be given the choice of how we contact you, either through telephone, email or postal address. When you purchase a ticket, you will be asked to opt in to our terms and conditions. This includes details on Tickets & Booking, Exchanges, Cancellations and refunds, Your Visit, Health & Safety and the nominated Child Protection Officer. For more information click here.
Your debit and credit card information
If you use your credit or debit card to purchase from us or to make a donation, we will ensure that this is carried out securely and in accordance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS).
We optionally allow you to store your card details for use in a future transaction. This is carried out in compliance with PCI-DSS and in a way where none of our staff members are able to see your full card number. We never store your 3 or 4 digit security code.
When you hear from us
We will contact you for marketing purposes depending on your preferences of how you would like to hear from us, however we will still contact you for reasons of legitimate interest. As part of the ticket purchasing process or event registration process we ask for your personal information, including your email, phone number and postal address. This information is stored on the ticketing software Spektrix. For more information, please see the Spektrix privacy notice.
Emails
Dotmailer, the email marketing software provider, is used for our communication with you, such as our marketing fortnightly What’s On email and show specific emails based on your interests. You will receive legitimate interest emails from Dotmailer or directly for the Lyric based on details around the show you are attending, to check our records are right and to check every now and then that you’re happy and satisfied. We gather statistics around email openings and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our emails. For more information, please see Dotmailer’s privacy notice. We don’t rent or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses. You can unsubscribe to marketing mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the end of any of our emails or by changing your account preferences. To review your account preferences click here.
Phone and Direct Mail
For legitimate reasons, such as timing changes or seating allocation, we will contact you by phone. For marketing purposes based on your preferences we will contact you on occasion by phone to make you aware of shows and special offers you may be interested in, or send you out information by direct mail relating to shows as the Lyric, such as the Season Brochure.
Visiting our Website
We use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to analyse the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. You can find more information on how cookies are used on this website in the Cookies Policy below.
If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.
Links to Other Web Sites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.
Third parties
There may be times in which we may disclose your personal information to specific named visiting companies whose performances you attend. In these cases, we will always ask for your explicit consent before doing so.
________________________________________
Cookies Policy
We use a system of classifying the different types of cookies which we use on the Website, or which may be used by third parties through our websites. The classification was developed by the International Chamber of Commerce UK and explains more about which cookies we use, why we use them, and the functionality you will lose if you decide you don’t want to have them on your device.
What is a cookie?
Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user’s device.
How long are cookies stored for?
Persistent cookies – these cookies remain on a user’s device for the period of time specified in the cookie. They are activated each time that the user visits the website that created that particular cookie.
Session cookies – these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and finishes when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies are deleted.
Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience.
You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.eu.
Cookies used on the Lyric Website
A list of all the cookies used on the Website by category is set out below:
Strictly necessary cookies
These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for. These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Website.
Performance cookies
These cookies collect anonymous information on the pages visited. By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
These cookies collect information about how visitors use the Website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how the Website works.
Functionality cookies
These cookies remember choices you make to improve your experience. By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device. These cookies allow the Website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
Third party cookies
These cookies allow third parties to track the success of their application or customise the application for you. Because of how cookies work we cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used on our site.
For example, if you choose to ‘share’ content through Twitter or other social networks you might be sent cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these cookies, so please check those websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.
________________________________________
Access to Your Personal Information
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, Cookies Policy, or how we process your information, please email info@lyrictheatre.co.uk
Changes to this Privacy Notice
We keep our privacy notice under regular review, complying with the current GDPR standards. This privacy notice was last updated on 21 May 2018.
________________________________________
This website is copyright Lyric Theatre NI.
All intellectual property rights are reserved.
The reproduction of any text, graphics, images, films or sound files, code, design or logo is forbidden without our written permission.
Our copyright and other intellectual property rights are protected by UK law.
CookiesThis site uses cookies:
